Now listen, yo!
（亮太(りょうた)）
おばあちゃん おばあちゃん…
People put your guns up
First I'll run dat
Run around and shoot them
（カヨ）大丈夫 亮太…
Brand new sound, yes still survival
Here comes the sound boy, live in this world
（亮太）お… おばあちゃん…
Intelligence, strength, and luck are swirling, flow
My swelled mind is candid
One punch to Banner in Savannah
An easy knockout, bam bam bam
（計(けい)）ンンッ… クッ…
One time for your mind, live through this
Around the world
It haunts me, the pain of the past
Around the noble god are borrowed things
When the seed that's sown flowers, whose is it
Live and fire the arrow of faith, more more more
There is no peace where you're going
Come on, stand up, don't give up the fight
Now, yes, this instant, die die die
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
（計）こいつ… なに？
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
あっ… ラ… ラスボス…
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Grandma...
Grandma!
Don't worry... Ryota...
What the hell is that thing?
It's... the final boss...
（計）ダメだ
It's no use...
I'll never survive this.
（計）絶対 助かんねえ これ
Am I...
（計）死ぬのかよ…
D
i
e
Please Die
...gonna die?
（計）俺…
Please Die
What now?
（北条(ほうじょう)）どうする？
（岸本(きしもと)）加藤(かとう)君は そこにいて
（加藤）えっ？
Kato, you wait here.
（北条）
ちょっと待て　俺と お前でか？
Wait a minute!
You mean it's just you and me?
You know how to use these guns, right?
（岸本）銃 使い方 分かるよね？
（加藤）俺にも…
Isn't there...
俺にも できることあるんじゃ…
（岸本）そこにいて
Isn't there something I can do, too?
Just wait here...
Please!
お願い
Something...
な… なんとか…
なんとかしねえと…
I've gotta do something!
Yuzo.
（鈴木星人）裕三(ゆうぞう)君？
（計）あっ…
ハッ… 撃って！
Fire!
More! MORE!
（岸本）もっと！ もっと！
（発射音）
Yuzo?
（鈴木星人）裕三君？
Damn! Not again!
ちくしょう… またかよ
Yuzo.
（鈴木星人たち）裕三君？
（鈴木星人）裕三君？
（計）な… 何だよ？ 裕三って
Who the hell is Yuzo anyway?
Yuzo.
お… おい
死なねえじゃんかよ こいつら！
Hey!
These guys aren't dying!
Why?
（岸本）なんで？
（鈴木星人たち）裕三君？
Yuzo.
裕三君？ 裕三君？
Yuzo!
Yuzo.
I'm NOT Yuzo, goddammit!
（計）裕三じゃねえっつうの！
Yuzo.
（鈴木星人たち）裕三君？
（計）何か答えりゃいいのかよ？
Am I supposed to say something?
Yuzo.
（鈴木星人たち）裕三君？
Yes... I am Yuzo.
（計）はい 裕三です　ンンッ…
（鈴木星人）スイカの名産地？
（計）えっ？
What place is famous for its watermelons?
Kantaro!
かんたろー
Refreshing...
爽やかな？
Hah!
ハァー ハァー ハァー…
Were you able to make some friends?
（鈴木星人）友達ができた？
Kagoshima?
（鈴木星人）鹿児島？
（鈴木星人）すばらしい
Wonderful.
（計）お… 落ち着け 落ち着け！
Okay, stay calm. Just relax...
Wonderful.
Sunday.
I should do something now,
while they're still smiling...
（計）ヤツらの顔が
笑っているうちに なんとか…
ウッ… 登ってきやがった
This thing just climbed up on me...
Ow!
（計）い… いってえ…
Ow...
Oh shit!
やっべえ…
It still hasn't turned to face me...
まだヤツは こっちを向いてない！
（計）今なら…
I still have a chance...
I might be able to...
今なら まだヤツを…
Both of them...
（北条）どっちも？
Yeah...
（加藤）ああ 守れなかった
We couldn't save either of them.
（春哉(はるや)）トロくせえ！
何やってんだ？ あいつ
What the hell's taking that idiot so long?
（電子音）
（北条）まだいる…
There's still more of them...
There's no end to it!
（岸本）キリがないよ
（加藤）時間は？
How much time left?
Only 15 minutes...
（北条）あと15分しかない
How many of us will survive this?
何人 生き残れるんだ？
I'm not gonna die...
（計）死んでたまるか
I'M NOT GONNA DIE!
（計）死んでたまるか！
（計）動くんじゃねえ！
Don't any of you move!
こいつ… こいつ やるぞ！
I'm gonna... I swear I'll kill him!
Is that what you want?
いいのかよ？
Shit!
（計）くそ！
ウ… ウソ… あっ…
No way!
（地響き）
（春哉・鉄男(てつお)）ウワッ！
（春哉）な… 何だ？
What was that?
I said I'm not gonna die!
し… 死んでたまるかー！
か… 神さま…
Oh please, God...
（ガラスの割れる音）
（春哉）ウワッ！
What the...
（春哉）何だ？
I... I did it.
（計）や… やった… やった！
I did it!
（天井のきしむ音）
あっ… や… やべえ！
Oh shit!
Hah, look at you now!
（計）
ざまあみろ　ざまあみろっつうの！
How ya like that, ya son of a bitch!
I showed you, you fucker!
（計）やったぜ ちくしょうめ！
（加藤）計ちゃん！
（計）あっ… よう 加藤
Kei!
Hey, Kato!
What the... What's going on?
（加藤）何だ？ どうなってんだ？
Heh! It's over!
（計）終わったぜ 全部！
Please Die
All of it!
Is this the end? Eh?
（加藤）“終わった”？
（計）ああ 全部 片づけた
It's over?
Yeah, I took care of everything.
I did it all by myself!
（計）
俺が１人でだ　これで終わりだ
Whoa...
I did it all by myself!
This is the end!
They really can't see us.
（鉄男）ホントに見えねえんだな
No...
（北条）いや…
Seems it's not over yet.
（北条）まだみてえだけど…
（計）えっ？
そんなはずねえよ！
No way!
アパートの下敷きになったんだぜ
（春哉の悲鳴）
That thing got completely
buried under the apartment!
Haruya!
（鉄男）春哉！
な… 何だ？ あれ　計ちゃん！
What the hell is that? Kei!
アア… 頭が…
The boss...
What's going on?
（岸本）何なの？
The boss was still alive!
頭が生きてやがった…
（鉄男・計）ウワッ！
（鉄男）は… 春哉…
Haruya...
何だ？ こいつ
What...
what is that?
Hm? Huh?
（男性）うん？ あっ なに？
ねらいは計ちゃんだ！
It's after Kei!
Run!
（加藤）逃げろ！
（計）逃げねえよ
I'm not going anywhere.
You think I'll run away?
（計）逃げてたまるかよ
ふざけんな
Gimme a break...
ふざけんなよ！
（岸本）玄野(くろの)君…
I've had enough of this!
Kurono...
ぶっ殺してやる！
I'll fucking kill you!
ウワ～ッ…
（咆哮）
（計）ウワ～ッ！
玄野君！
Kurono!
Kei!
（加藤）計ちゃーん！
アアッ… い… いってえ…
Ouch!
Damn...
That hurts, you son of a bitch!
痛(いて)えっつってんだ この野郎！
ウワッ！
ウワッ… ウッ！
ンンッ… 離せよ！
Let go of me!
Damn it!
（計）くそ！ ウッ！
Kei!
計ちゃん！
You... you piece of shit!
こ… こんちくしょう！
I'm not going down like this!
死ぬかよー！
ウワッ… ンンッ…
Damn...
（計）ウワ～ッ！
ウワッ！ アッ…
Kei!
（加藤）計ちゃん！
（岸本）玄野君！
Kurono!
（加藤）計ちゃん！
Kei!
計ちゃん！
Kurono!
（岸本）玄野君！
Kei! Are you all right?
（加藤）計ちゃん 大丈夫か？
Kei!
（加藤）計ちゃん！
I... I think so...
な… なんとか…
（加藤）
あっ… 良かった… 良かった
Thank God! Thank God...
Hey, is it over?
（鉄男）おい 終わったのかよ？
I guess...
（北条）
多分　カウンターが止まってる
It stopped counting down.
Whoa!
（鉄男）ウワッ！
（岸本）うん？
Back to that room again?
（鉄男）また この部屋かよ
I guess that's all of us.
（加藤）これで全員か…
随分 減ってしまった
It's a lot fewer than before...
Well I'm glad you're still alive.
（岸本）良かった　生きてたんだ？
Hey! Can we get out of here?
（鉄男）
おい 帰れんのか？ こっから
I'm happy for you.
Hey! Can we get out of here?
Yeah, but there's still the scoring first...
（加藤）ああ　まだ採点があるけど
Scores, huh?
採点か… あっ…
That mess is all cleaned up...
片づいてる…
Okay. Hear are
your scores.
（岸本）あっ… 採点だ
Hey, the rating started.
Okay. Hear are
your scores.
Dog
0 points
You have no motivation.
DO something, goddammit!
（計）フン！
"Do something"?
（計）“何かしろ”だって
犬にムリ言うなよ
C'mon, he's a dog!
What do these scores mean anyway?
何の意味があんだよ？ 採点って
If what Nishi told us is true,
（加藤）
西の言ったことが本当なら―
この点数が100点たまると
自由になれるはずだが…
then you're supposed to be set free
when you reach 100.
（北条）何なんだよ？ 一体
What the hell?
This seriously isn't some kind of game?
マジでゲームじゃねえのか？
Dog
0 points
You have no motivation.
DO something, goddammit!
Miss Melons
10 points
Total 10 points
Only 90 points to go!
もう… なに？ 巨乳って
Miss Melons? What are you talking about?
It says, 90 points to go...
“あと90点で終わり”って
書いてある
Does it mean I'm gonna be free?
自由になれるってこと？
Oh!
あっ… １人５点だ
It's 5 points each!
Because I killed two so far...
私 ２人やっつけたから
Miss Melons
10 points
Total 10 points
Only 90 points to go!
Kato-cha:)
5 points
tOTAL 5 points
Only 95 points to go!
Kato-cha:)
5 points
tOTAL 5 points
Only 95 points to go!
What?!
Kato-cha:)
5 points
tOTAL 5 points
Only 95 points to go!
But you fought so many of those things!
あんな数相手に
戦ってたのに…
Kato-cha:)
5 points
tOTAL 5 points
Only 95 points to go!
Kato-cha:)
5 points
tOTAL 5 points
Only 95 points to go!
Yeah...
（加藤）いや 実際に
死なせたのは１体だけだ
Yeah...
But I only killed one of them.
I get it!
あっ そうか　数倒せば
それだけ早く自由になれる
The more you kill,
the sooner you're set free.
That means I have to keep on
doing this, and survive...
あと何回も参加して
生き残んなきゃならないのか…
Kato-cha:)
5 points
tOTAL 5 points
Only 95 points to go!
Sadako
0 points
You follow that fag around too much.
And you also disappear too much.
Sadako
0 points
You follow that fag around too much.
And you also disappear too much.
Sadako?
（計）〝サダコ〞？
サダコって誰だ？
Who's that?
Her! She's hiding over there!
（岸本）あそこ　隠れてる
（計）あっ…
Following the fag?
（計）“ホモのあと”？
（北条）あっ…
Who's that supposed to be?
（計）ホモって誰だ？
Maybe one of the guys who died was gay.
（北条）死んだヤツの中に
いたんじゃねえの？
（計）ウウッ…
（北条）何だよ？
What?
The Fag
10 points
Total 10 points
Only 90 points to go!
Wha...
（北条）ち… 違うっつうの
Hey, I'm not gay!
Gimme a fuckin' break!
ふざけんな てめえら！
Stay the hell away from me!
I'll frickin' kill ya!
近づくな てめえ！ 殺すぞ！
だ… 誰が お前なんか…
What makes you think I'd even...
（一同）ウッ…
（計）マジかよ？
No way!
C'mon, Kato, leave him alone!
もう 加藤君まで
いいじゃない ホモだって
So what if he's gay?
But I'm not... I'm not gay!
ホモじゃ… ホモじゃねえ！
The Fag
10 points
Total 10 points
Only 90 points to go!
Bikie
number 1
0 points
You've got an unpleasant look in your eyes.
And you're too bossy.
Oh, is that me?
（鉄男）ああ 俺か
What the hell's this bullshit!
…んだ？ これ　ちくしょう！
Bikie
number 1
0 points
You've got an unpleasant look in your eyes.
And you're too bossy.
Errand Boy
38 points
Total 38 points
Only 62 points to go!
Errand Boy
38 points
Total 38 points
Only 62 points to go!
What the hell?
（鉄男）ああ？
なんで こいつだけ？
Errand Boy
38 points
Total 38 points
Only 62 points to go!
How come he got so many points?
That's awesome, Kei!
（加藤）すっげえ 計ちゃん！
（岸本）
すっご～い 38点　なんで？
Whoa, cool! 38 points!
But how?
Errand boy...
（計）パシリって俺？
Is that ME?
Whoa! It actually opened!
（鉄男）おお…
マジで開くじゃねえか おお…
このまま家(うち)に帰れんだな
So we can go home now?
I wonder where she's going to go home to?
（計）どこに帰るんだろう？
I'm not sure how many days from now,
（加藤）
何日後か分からねえけど―
but we should end up seeing
each other in that room again.
また あの部屋で
会うことになるはずだ
So I guess I'll be seeing you...
よろしくな これから
Um, Kato?
（岸本）加藤君
（加藤）うん？
You don't... um...
加藤君は
１人暮らしとかじゃないよね？
You don't live by yourself
or anything, do you?
Uh, well... Actually my brother and I
live with one of our relatives.
えっ？ 俺 弟と一緒に
親戚ん家(ち)に間借りしてんだよ
なんで？
Why?
（岸本）
あっ… 何でもない　何でも…
Oh... it's nothing!
Really!
ただ聞いてみただけだから
I was just curious, that's all!
帰ろう
（計）あっ…
Okay, well, let's go!
チェッ…
Damn...
（計）今回も なんとか生き延びた
Somehow I managed to survive again.
けど なんかヘコむな…
But...
Well... this kind of sucks.
We all start out as pure and innocent babes
Even if you taste the bitter fruit,
don't be discouraged, walk straight
I know it's in the past, but the rain still stings
I'm lonely as floating ice
I kiss your thin finger
And remember you crying
Even if this is the end
I won't forget your last kiss
I won't forget
I won't forget his kiss
（鉄男）牛乳を飲まなければ
赤ん坊は育たないこともある
Children need to drink milk in order to
grow up strong and healthy.
You could say that milk and breast milk
are two of humanity's greatest treasures...
とにかく 牛乳と母乳は人類の宝だ
バカ野郎
俺は死にたくねえんだよ！
Ah, enough of this crap!
I don't wanna die!
次回 “さようなら”
Next time: Goodbye.